# CAN GUDEN

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER & DESIGN STUDENT

#### CONTACT DETAILS

- >> January 10, 1992, Amsterdam, The Netherlands
- >> Dutch
- >> Orchideelaan 173, 1171 MG, Badhoevedorp, The Netherlands
- >> hello@cngdn.com
- >> www.cngdn.com
- >> Github: canguden

Mobile No. +31(0)6 242 678 31

#### **ALL ABOUT ME**

I am a student web developer with a strong eye for innovative design and a keen understanding of techniques geared toward optimum user experience. passionate and dedicated to learn and develop. Interested in Javascript and Python. Willing to learn a new programming language. Focussing mostly on UI/UX design. Interested in back-end development and eager in solving complex problems.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### >> Marble Hotels, Ibiza, Spain

Food and Beverage Assistant Manager | 2018 - 2020 Managed the food and beverage department focussing on marketing, creating and designing campaigns, menus, flyers.

#### >> Skybar 747, Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Assistant Manager | 2017-2021

- > Developing and creating a team
- > Developing menu's
- > Marketing and Sales
- > Handling cash draws
- > Reporting to general manager

### >> Corendon Hotels, Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Shop Manager | 2016 - 2018

- > Managed a little shop selling foods and goods
- > Direct Sales
- > Handling the Cashier
- > Designed flyers
- > Created promotions to generate more income

#### >> Imagine Innovations V.O.F. Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Co-Founder | 2014 - 2015

- > Created a software for mobile ordering.
- > Set-up a business
- > Penetrated the market with an unknown product at a very early stage, difficulty finding partners.
- > Marketed the product and sold
- > Learned from the business aspect as a young entrepreneur

# EDUCATION HISTORY

# >> Code Institute, Dublin, Ireland

Full Stack Developer | 2021 - present

Learning programming online, using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, MongoDB, Flask, PHP, MySQL

# >> RocvA MBO-4, Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Markting & Communication Degree | Class of 2014

# COMPETENCIES

HTML

CSS

Python
Javascript

MySQL

Django
Flask

**■■■■** Wordpress/Elementor

■■■■ MongoDB

# SOFTWARE

- > Microsoft Office
- > Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator & inDesign
- > VS Code
- > Github

# OTHER INTERESTS

- > Role and growth of technology in societal growth.
- > Development of local businesses
- > Community involvement and outreach
- > Learning foreign languages

#### LANGUAGES

- > Dutch Native
- > Turkish Mother Tongue
- > English Fluent
- > Spanish Fluent
- > German Advanced